

CONTACT

786-710-2309

Johnnymorrisportfolio@gmail.com

Killeen, TX

in linkedin.com/in/Jonathanmorris-333396142

EDUCATION

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Midwood High School, Charlotte, NC 2000 – 2004

EXPERTISE

PROFESSIONAL

- Collaboration
- Adaptability
- Problem Solving

TECHNICAL

- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft Excel
- Data Analysis

JONATHAN MORRIS

P R O F E S S I O N A L T I T L E

SUMMARY

Expert sales manager with over 10 years of sales experience, adept at building a customer base to increase revenue and consistently exceed sales target. Excellent communication skills with the ability to build strong relationships and customer satisfaction. Looking to utilize expertise with organizations in Software sales and marketing.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Retail Sales Lead

Spectrum, Orlando, FL

2018 - 2021

Making sure all employees had a well-oiled machine to work in. Responsible for over \$100k in inventory and maintaining 25% Growth month over month. Also coaching and developing all employees in location and guiding them into management roles company wide. Also responsible for maintaining and increasing small business sales month over month for my region by coaching all RSM's and offering best practices as well as helping guide the reps throughout the relationship

Institutional Sales & Marketing Support

Broxton Capital, San Juan, Puerto Rico

2017 - 2018

Client relationships liaison in charge of selling to and gaining new clients by uncovering the need for our value investing method. Also responsible for creating and maintaining relationships with key contacts inside major investment and hedge funds

Business Sales Manager

2016 – 2017

T-Mobile, Kissimmee, FL

Manage the business by triaging workload to address high-impact tasks. Partner with sales reps to manage a portfolio of high-value business customers; all with complex needs. Partner closely with Implementation team to map out customer onboarding plan and objectives. Anticipate and resolve customer pain points by bringing appropriate resources and solutions. Maintain a holistic understanding of current and future TFB products/services; drive adoption within assigned accounts by identifying additional solutions and prepare quotes for new product/service offerings to deliver customer outcomes.

Prioritizing leads based upon the sales cycle of the lead.

Coached and developed RSM's to teach Reps on how to uncover qualified leads. Visiting retail locations to help reps close and initiate business sales and leads. Using CRM's to maintain and gauge client relationships to uncover opportunities Scheduling visits to potential clients business locations to uncover pain points Overcoming client objections by creating value around the suite of products offered by the company

Retail Sales Manager

2014-2016

T-Mobile, Kissimmee, FL

Making sure all employees had a well oiled machine to work in. Responsible for over \$100k in inventory and maintaining 25% Growth month over month. Also coaching and developing all employees in location and guiding them into management roles company wide. Also responsible for maintaining and increasing small business business month over month for my area by coaching all RSM's and offering best practices as well as helping guide the reps throughout the

AWARDS

AWARD NAME

Organization

Year Here

AWARD NAME

Organization

Year Here

AWARD NAME

Organization

Year Here

COMMUNITY INVOLVMENT

ORGANIZATION

Volunteer Role Location, Date

ORGANIZATION

Volunteer Role

Location, Date

ORGANIZATION

Volunteer Role

Location, Date

INTERESTS

Limit the number of hobbies you include to 5 at most and be as specific as possible.

Here are some examples:

- BBC Click & documentaries
- 10 years of guitar playing
- Completing DIY projects
- Running marathons
- Sign language

Business Sales

AT&T, Kissimmee, FL

Responsible for selling all AT&T suite of products (mobile devices, home solutions, business essentials and fiber needs) to the general public. Also maintaining a close relationship with all business customers who visited the location and growing with the customer as their needs change. Responsible for growing the amount of business certified representatives in the retail location as well as the market and coaching and observing all representatives and implementing best practices market wide Ensure you tailor your resume to each and every job in order to improve your chances of getting an interview.

- Use action verbs to transform your job duties into something valuable. The guide that came with your order gives some ways to do this.
- Customized resumes that align with job requirements and include keywords from the
 job description will stand out to recruiters who often receive hundreds of resumes per
 role.
- Once you have crafted your impressive resume, you must save it as a PDF document before uploading or sending to hiring managers.

Sales Representative

AT&T, Killeen, TX

2010 - 2012

Responsible for selling all AT&T suite of products (mobile devices, home solutions, business essentials and fiber needs) to the general public. Also maintaining a close relationship with all business customers who visited the location and growing with the customer as their needs change. Responsible for growing the amount of business certified representatives in the retail location as well as the market and coaching and observing all representatives and implementing best practices market wide Ensure you tailor your resume to each and every job in order to improve your chances of getting an interview.

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

Coding Bootcamp

NuCamp, Remote

2021 - 2021

- Dedicated over 1,000 hours of intensive hands-on training to develop dozens of web applications in React, React Native, and JavaScript
- Utilized a multitude of frameworks such as React & React-Native
- Created user-friendly sites utilizing CRUD operations and RESTful routes together with API Integration
- Collaborated to Implement front-end and back-end solutions to unique challenges and wire-frame specifications

2012-2013